yamaha.com 2019-03-10

# Privacy Policy - Yamaha Corporation

Last update : 2006/10/23

## Your Consent to this Privacy Policy

By accessing, browsing or using the Yamaha web site or providing us with Personal Information, as defined below, you signify that you agree to the terms of our current Privacy Policy as posted in this page of the site. If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, please do not access, browse or use the site or provide us with Personal Information.  
The Yamaha web site you have entered is operated by or on behalf of Yamaha Corporation. We, Yamaha Corporation, comply with the laws and regulations regarding personal data protection, and place great importance on protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy prescribes the type of information that we collect, and how we use and manage such information.

## Collection of Personal Information

"Personal Information", as referenced in this Privacy Policy, means personally identifiable information including, without limitation, your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address.  
When you are visiting our site, you may be asked for Personal Information to allow you to order Yamaha products or services, participate in sales promotion services or prize competitions, answer our questionnaires or inquiries by e-mail or through the web site, register as a Yamaha user, monitor Yamaha products, or e-mail news services concerning the Yamaha product lines, etc.  
We will not collect any Personal Information unless and until you provide such information to us voluntarily. When you provide us with Personal Information, you authorize us to use such information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.  
If you do not agree with any term in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your Personal Information. Certain services may be conditioned on the provision of your Personal Information.

## How We Use Your Information

When we collect your Personal Information, we reasonably specify the purpose of such collection.  
Any Personal Information that you provide will be used to meet your request such as forwarding Yamaha products, brochures, magazines, etc. and offering certain services. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you regarding other products and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to be contacted by us concerning other products or services that may be of interest to you, you can request that we limit our contact with you to the express purpose that you provided your Personal Information.

## Cookies

Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer's hard disk drive when you visit a web site. We use cookies as a tool to allow us to customize your experience to better match your interests and preferences, or to simply facilitate your signing in to use the services. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can set your computer to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being stored. If you refuse to use cookies, our ability to provide you with personalized services would be limited.  
Please refer to your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

## Share of Personal Information With Third Parties

We do not, in principle, share any Personal Information with any third parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. We may retain third parties to act as our agent to analyze data we collect, including Personal Information, solely to help us improve our products, services and web sites.  
Otherwise, we may disclose your Personal Information to the distributing company delivering Yamaha products or other materials and to the bank transferring the expenses from your account.  
Also your inquiry may be directed to the third parties such as Yamaha group companies for your convenience depending upon the subject of your inquiry. These third parties are expressly prohibited from using or disclosing your Personal Information in any other way.  
Please note that we will release Personal Information if in our opinion we are required or authorized to do so by or pursuant to laws or regulations, or by a search warrant, subpoena, court order or other legal process.

## Changes in Our Policy

We reserve the right to alter or remove this Privacy Policy at any time in our discretion. Whenever we make any alteration to this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes here. Therefore, we advise you to visit this page frequently to stay informed. When you use our services after the alteration of this Privacy Policy, you signify that you agree to the alteration of this Privacy Policy.

## Who to Contact

Please write to us from Other Inquiries page in Customer Support page or other customer support service web sites linked to the web site through which you use our service, if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or requests to correct, add to, update, or delete your Personal Information.  
Before we receive your offer to correct, add to, update, or delete Personal Information, we may verify your identity to prevent Personal Information from being altered unlawfully.
